I CAN'T BELIEVE
MY LITTLE BROTHER
IS MARRIED.
I KNOW.
( squeals )
YOU GUYS, WHY
DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
YOU WERE ELOPING?
WE WERE AT THE COURTHOUSE.
WE WERE HAVING LUNCH...
WAIT. WHY WERE YOU
AT THE COURTHOUSE?
WE WERE HAVING LUNCH.
YEAH, AND THEN
ALL OF A SUDDEN, WE WERE, LIKE
"HEY, YOU KNOW, WE'RE HERE.
WE'RE HAVING LUNCH.
LET'S GET MARRIED!" RIGHT?
WOW. A YEAR
AND A HALF AGO
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
I HAD A BROTHER.
NOW I HAVE
A SISTER, TOO.
( all laughing )
OH, IT'S SO
GREAT. OH...
( moaning )
OKAY.
STOP IT. DON'T.
OH.
SO, OOH, I'M GOING
TO GET YOU A GIFT NOW.
IS THERE
ANYTHING YOU NEED?
OH... YEAH.
WE'VE BEEN TRYING
TO GET PREGNANT
UH, PRETTY MUCH EVER SINCE
WE GOT ENGAGED.
THOUGHT WE'D GET
A JUMP ON THINGS.
YOU KNOW, NO ONE'S
GETTING ANY YOUNGER.
( laughing )
'CAUSE THE THING IS
UM, WE'RE NOT ABLE TO,
YOU KNOW
UH, CONCEIVE,
YOU KNOW?
AND WE'VE TRIED EVERYTHING.
WE'VE SEEN
A BUNCH OF DOCTORS.
YEAH, AND THEY...
THEY SAY THAT...
THAT OUR ONLY CHANCE
TO HAVE A BABY
IS IF THEY TAKE MY SPERM
HER EGG, AND PUT IT
TOGETHER IN A DISH
AND THEN PUT IT
INTO ANOTHER GIRL.
SO WE WERE WONDERING
IF YOU COULD BE THE GIRL
THAT WE COULD PUT IT INTO.
THAT'S A REALLY
NICE GIFT.
I WAS THINKING OF,
LIKE, A GRAVY BOAT.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS STUCK
IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY! YOU GUYS.
CHECK IT OUT,
CHECK IT OUT.
GUESS WHAT JOB
I JUST GOT.
I DON'T KNOW, BUT DONALD TRUMP
WANTS HIS BLUE BLAZER BLACK.
WHAT?
BLUE BLAZER BACK.
HE-HE WANTS IT BACK.
WELL, Y-YOU SAID "BLACK."
WHY WOULD HE WANT
HIS BLUE BLAZER BLACK?
WELL, YOU-YOU KNOW WHAT I MEANT.
NO. YOU'VE MESSED IT UP.
YOU'RE STUPID.
SO, WHAT JOB DID YOU GET, JOE?
OH. UH, TOUR GUIDE
AT THE MUSEUM.
YEAH. ROSS
GOT IT FOR ME.
DON'T YOU HAVE TO BE
A DINOSAUR EXPERT OR SOMETHING?
NO, NOT REALLY.
THEY GIVE YOU ALL
THE INFORMATION.
IT'S, UH, IT'S LIKE
MEMORIZING A SCRIPT. YEAH.
"AND ON YOUR LEFT,
YOU HAVE TYRANNOSAURUS REX
A CARNIVORE
FROM THE JURASSIC PERIOD."
( appreciative remarks )
UH, ACTUALLY, JOEY
IT'S THE
CRETACEOUS PERIOD.
YEAH, BUT I CAN
PRONOUNCE "JURASSIC."
All:
HEY.
HEY!
GUESS WHAT?
FRANK, JR. AND ALICE
GOT MARRIED.
( excited comments )
AND THEY'RE HAVING A BABY.
( all gasping )
AND, AND, THEY WANT ME TO
GROW IT FOR THEM IN MY UTERUS.
OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH.
YOU'RE REALLY THINKING
OF HAVING SEX
WITH YOUR BROTHER?
EWW! AND, OH NO!
IT'S... THEY WANT ME
TO BE THE SURROGATE.
IT'S HER EGG AND HIS SPERM,
AND I'M-I'M JUST THE OVEN.
IT'S TOTALLY THEIR BUN.
OH.
WHAT DID YOU TELL THEM?
WELL, THEY SAID
I HAD TO THINK ABOUT IT FIRST
BUT WHAT IS THERE TO THINK OF?
I'M GOING TO BE GIVING SOMEONE
THE GREATEST GIFT
YOU CAN POSSIBLY GIVE.
YOU'RE GOING TO CARRY
THEIR CHILD AND GET THEM
A SONY PLAY STATION?
HONEY, THIS REALLY IS AN
INCREDIBLE THING TO DO FOR THEM
BUT THERE ARE THINGS
TO THINK ABOUT.
YEAH. I MEAN,
YOU'D BE PREGNANT.
I MEAN, PREGNANT.
I KNOW.
PHEEBS, YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT PUTTING YOUR BODY
THROUGH AN AWFUL LOT.
I MEAN, MORNING SICKNESS,
UH... LABOR
AND IT'S ALL
FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
YEAH. WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
WELL, THE STUFF
I JUST MENTIONED.
WOW. I DON'T KNOW
IF I COULD EVER DO THAT.
YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS FIGURED
THE FIRST TIME I HAD A BABY
IT WOULD BE WITH SOMEONE I LOVE,
AND THAT BABY WAS, YOU KNOW...
A KEEPER.
YOU KNOW, YOU GUYS WERE
A LOT MORE SUPPORTIVE
WHEN I WANTED
TO MAKE DENIM FURNITURE.
PHEEBS, LISTEN,
IF YOU DECIDE TO DO THIS
WE'LL BE SUPPORTIVE
LIKE CRAZY.
YEAH.
JUST THINK
IT THROUGH.
TALK TO SOMEBODY
WHO'S HAD A BABY.
LIKE YOUR MOM.
MY MOM NEVER GAVE BIRTH.
OH, BUT MY BIRTH MOM DID.
MMM, I LOVE THIS TUSHIE.
CAN I TAKE IT
TO WORK WITH ME?
OH, YEAH, SURE.
IT'S NOT MINE ANYWAY.
IT CAME WITH THE PANTS.
OH.
I AM SO JEALOUS.
YOU GUYS ARE REALLY
JUST RIGHT THERE, AREN'T YOU?
YES.
RIGHT WHERE?
THE BEGINNING WHERE...
YOU KNOW, IT'S ALL SEX
AND TALKING AND SEX
AND TALKING AND...
YEAH. YOU-YOU GOT TO LOVE
THE TALKING.
AND THE SEX?
WE HAVEN'T HAD SEX YET.
OKAY, BUT WHAT'S
THE BIG DEAL, YOU KNOW?
THIS IS SPECIAL,
AND I WANT OUR LOVE TO GROW
BEFORE WE MOVE
ON TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
OH, CHANDLER,
THAT IS SO NICE.
THAT IS REALLY NICE...
LYING.
NO WAY IS THAT
THE REASON.
WHY?
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
NOT MATURE ENOUGH TO UNDERSTAND?
NO, HE'S RIGHT.
I'M TOTALLY LYING.
THEN WHAT IS IT?
WELL, KATHY'S LAST BOYFRIEND
WAS JOEY.
AND YOU'RE AFRAID
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO...
"FILL HIS SHOES."
NO, I'M AFRAID I WON'T BE ABLE
TO MAKE LOVE AS WELL AS HIM.
YEAH. I WAS GOING
FOR THE METAPHOR.
YES, AND I WAS SAYING
THE ACTUAL WORDS.
Monica:
WELL, BIG DEAL.
SO JOEY'S HAD A
LOT OF GIRLFRIENDS.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
HE'S GREAT IN BED.
WE SHARE A WALL.
SO EITHER HE'S GREAT IN BED
OR SHE JUST LIKED
TO AGREE WITH HIM A LOT.
SWEETIE, WITH YOU, IT'S
GOING TO BE DIFFERENT.
THE SEX IS GOING
TO BE GREAT
'CAUSE YOU-YOU
GUYS ARE IN LOVE.
YEAH?
Rachel:
YEAH.
JUST GO FOR IT, CHANDLER.
YEAH. YOU SHOULD.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SLEEP WITH MY GIRLFRIEND
BUT I'M JUST DOING IT
FOR YOU GUYS.
OKAY. NOW THE MASTODON IS FROM
THE SEMI-LATE JURASSIC PERIOD.
ISN'T THE MASTODON
FROM THE PLIOCENE EPOCH?
SHH. THIS IS A MUSEUM.
NO TALKING.
OKAY. RIGHT DOWN HERE,
WE HAVE...
A LARGE FOOT.
UH... AND OVER HERE,
WE HAVE ROSS GELLER.
EVERYONE WAVE
HI TO ROSS.
ROSS IS ONE OF OUR MOST
IMPORTANT SCIENTISTS.
LOOK AT HIM
HARD AT WORK.
OKAY. MOVING
RIGHT ALONG.
COME ON.
( knocking on door )
IT'S OPEN.
COME IN.
HI.
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
IT GAVE ME TIME TO FINISH,
UH, GLAZING MY NIPPLES.
WOW. YOU REALLY GO ALL OUT
WHEN YOU'RE EXPECTING COMPANY.
NO, I WAS WORKING ON MY POTTERY.
OH. OH! OH, I DIDN'T KNOW
THAT YOU DID...
POT.
WELL, YEAH, UH,
MOSTLY NUDES.
IT COMBINES
MY TWO PASSIONS:
POTTERY AND EROTICA.
OH. OOH! "ERROTERY."
HEY! OKAY.
WELL, THANKS FOR
COMING OUT TO SEE ME.
I JUST THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE A VERY GOOD IDEA
TO TALK ABOUT THIS
BABY STUFF IN PERSON.
OKAY.
( sighs )
I DON'T THINK IT'S
A VERY GOOD IDEA.
WHY NOT?
WELL, BECAUSE YOU'D
BE GIVING UP A BABY
AND I-I REALLY DON'T...
I DON'T KNOW IF
THERE'S ANYTHING
THAT I COULD SAY
THAT COULD MAKE YOU
UNDERSTAND THE PAIN
OF GIVING UP
A BABY, SO...
UM...
( gasps )
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I UNDERSTAND THE PAIN.
DON'T-DON'T HURT THE PUPPY.
NO, NO, NO.
THE PUPPY IS YOURS.
OH, I GET A PUPPY?
WELL, YEAH.
I MEAN, BUT FOR
ONLY THREE DAYS.
WHY?
WELL, YOU KNOW
I-I REALIZE THAT I
DON'T HAVE ANY RIGHT
TO START GETTING
ALL PARENTY ON YOU
AND EVERYTHING NOW
BUT, UM... UH...
PHOEBE, WOULD YOU
PLEASE LOOK AT ME
AND NOT THE PUPPY?
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
OKAY.
I MEAN, I KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
I GAVE UP TWO BABIES
AND I ONLY WISH
THAT I HAD SOMEONE THERE
WHO HAD GIVEN UP BABIES
THAT COULD HAVE TOLD ME
HOW TERRIBLE IT IS
TO GIVE UP BABIES.
( sighing softly )
I JUST THINK
THAT IT WOULD BE SOMETHING
THAT YOU WOULD REGRET
EVERY SINGLE DAY FOR THE REST
OF YOUR LIFE.
SO, HOWEVER HARD IT IS
FOR YOU TO GIVE UP
THIS PUPPY, OH...
WOULD BE, LIKE, A MILLION TIMES
HARDER TO GIVE UP A CHILD.
I REALLY SHOULDN'T
HAVE GIVEN YOU
THE PUPPY FIRST.
ALL RIGHT. IT'S OKAY.
( sighs )
OH, UH, WOULD YOU
MIND SITTING THERE?
I-I'M SAVING THIS SEAT
FOR MY FRIEND, ROSS.
YOU MEAN, DR. GELLER?
"DOCTOR"? OH, I DIDN'T KNOW
HE HAD A NICKNAME.
OH, HE WON'T SIT HERE.
ONLY THE PEOPLE
IN THE WHITE COATS
SIT OVER THERE
AND ONLY THE PEOPLE
IN THE BLUE BLAZERS
SIT OVER HERE.
WELL, UH, H-HOW COME?
THAT'S THE WAY IT IS.
THAT'S CRAZY.
MAYBE IT'S CRAZY
IN A PERFECT WORLD--
A WORLD WITHOUT LAB COATS
AND BLAZERS--
BUT YOU NOT
IN A PERFECT WORLD.
YOU IN A MUSEUM NOW.
SEE THAT SCIENTIST
WITH THE GLASSES?
HE AND I USED TO PLAY
TOGETHER ALL THE TIME
IN GRADE SCHOOL.
HMM, BUT NOW...
PETER!
HEY, PETER!
IT'S ME, RHONDA
FROM P.S. 129!
I SHARED MY PUDDING
WITH YOU, MAN.
I GAVE YOU MY SNACK PACK!
SEE? HE PRETEND
HE DON'T EVEN HEAR ME!
I-I THINK
EVERYBODY'S
PRETENDING
THEY DON'T HEAR YOU.
LOOK, I...
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
YOU AND YOUR JACKETS
AND YOUR SEPARATE TABLES
BUT ROSS IS ONE
OF MY BEST FRIENDS
AND IF I SAVE HIM A SEAT
I'M TELLING YOU,
HE WILL SIT IN IT.
ROSS, ROSS,
OVER HERE, MAN.
I SAVED YOU A SEAT.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'M COOL OVER HERE.
I'LL CATCH UP WITH
YOU LATER, JOEY.
OOP, THIS IS SAVED.
GIFT SHOP.
HEY, UH...
I'M REALLY, REALLY SORRY
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE CAFETERIA TODAY.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL, YOU KNOW.
YOU-YOU DO
WHAT YOU GOT TO DO, RIGHT?
IT'S NOT JUST ME.
I MEAN, THE SCIENTISTS
AND THE TOUR GUIDES
NEVER SIT TOGETHER.
WHATEVER.
IT'S LIKE THAT
EVERYWHERE, JOEY.
OKAY, MON, BACK ME UP HERE.
WHERE YOU WORK
THE, UH, THE WAITERS EAT
WITH THE WAITERS, RIGHT
AND THE CHEFS EAT
WITH THE OTHER CHEFS, RIGHT?
UH, I EAT BY MYSELF
IN THE ALLEY
BECAUSE EVERYBODY HATES ME.
LOOK, ROSS...
REALLY, IT'S-IT'S
NO BIG DEAL.
YOU KNOW,
YOU WEAR A WHITE COAT.
I WEAR A BLUE BLAZER.
IF THAT MEANS WE CAN'T
BE FRIENDS AT WORK
THEN SO BE IT, YOU KNOW.
HEY, I UNDERSTAND,
YOU KNOW?
WHEN I'M IN A PLAY
AND YOU'RE
IN THE AUDIENCE
I DON'T TALK TO YOU, RIGHT?
SO, IT'S... YOU KNOW,
IT'S, UH, IT'S-IT'S COOL.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
( door opening and closing )
YEAH. WHEN WE'RE
IN THE AUDIENCE
HE DOESN'T TALK TO US,
BUT HE DOES WAVE.
( Phoebe humming
"Rock a Bye Baby" )
( door opening )
HI.
( continues humming )
WHY'S PHOEBE SINGING
TO KARL MALDEN?
OOH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR PUPPY
TO GO OUT AGAIN.
COME ON. LET'S GO
TO THE BALCONY.
WHAT?
UH... THE STREET.
COME ON.
LET'S GO TO THE STREET.
OH, LISTEN,
DON'T GO ON THE BALCONY
UNTIL AFTER I GET BACK.
( door closing )
SO... DID YOU DO IT?
YES, YES, WE HAD THE SEX.
UH-OH. IT WAS BAD?
IT WAS FINE, YOU KNOW,
BUT SHE DIDN'T AGREE WITH ME
AS STRONGLY
AS SHE AGREED WITH JOEY.
SHE WAS MORE, LIKE, UH
"OH, I SEE YOUR POINT.
( noncommittal: )
I'M ALL RIGHT WITH IT."
WELL, I MEAN,
IT WAS THE FIRST TIME.
YOU KNOW,
THERE'S NOT ALWAYS
A LOT OF AGREEMENT
THE FIRST TIME.
YEAH. NOT FOR
GIRLS ANYWAY.
GUYS AGREE...
LIKE THAT.
LOOK, YOU HAVE
TO HELP ME, OKAY?
I MEAN, I KNOW WHAT
TO DO WITH A WOMAN.
YOU KNOW, I KNOW
WHERE EVERYTHING GOES.
IT'S ALWAYS... NICE,
BUT I NEED TO KNOW
WHAT MAKES IT GO FROM NICE
TO "MY GOD, SOMEBODY'S
KILLING HER IN THERE."
ALL RIGHT. I'M GOING
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING
A LOT OF GUYS DON'T KNOW.
RACH, HAND ME
THAT PAD, PLEASE.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW...
WELL, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DRAW
AN ACTUAL WO...
WHOA, SHE'S HOT.
NOW, EVERYBODY KNOWS
THE BASIC EROGENOUS ZONES.
YOU GOT ONE, TWO, THREE...
FOUR...
FIVE...
SIX AND SEVEN.
THERE ARE SEVEN?
LET ME SEE THAT.
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S ONE?
( chuckling )
KIND OF AN IMPORTANT ONE.
OH, YOU KNOW...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WAS LOOKING AT
IT UPSIDE DOWN.
( laughs )
WELL, YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES THAT HELPS.
OKAY. NOW, MOST GUYS WILL HIT,
UH, ONE, TWO, THREE
AND THEN GO TO SEVEN
AND SET UP CAMP.
TH-THAT'S BAD?
WELL, IF YOU GO TO DISNEYLAND
YOU DON'T SPEND THE WHOLE DAY
ON THE MATTERHORN.
WELL, YOU MIGHT, IF IT
WERE ANYTHING LIKE SEVEN.
Monica:
ALL RIGHT.
UH, THE IMPORTANT THING
IS TO TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU WANT TO HIT THEM ALL
AND YOU WANT TO MIX THEM UP.
YOU GOT TO KEEP THEM
ON THEIR TOES.
OH, TOES!
YEAH...
FOR SOME PEOPLE.
Monica:
ALL RIGHT.
YOU COULD, UH
START OUT WITH
A-A LITTLE ONE...
A TWO...
A ONE, TWO, THREE...
A THREE...
A FIVE...
A FOUR...
A THREE, TWO...
TWO...
A TWO, FOUR, SIX...
TWO, FOUR, SIX...
FOUR...
TWO...
FOUR, SEVEN...
FIVE, SEVEN...
SIX, SEVEN...
SEVEN...
SEVEN, SEVEN,
SEVEN, SEVEN, SEVEN...
SEVEN!
( silently: )
SEVEN.
DR. GELLER...
THERE'S A SEAT OVER HERE.
THANK YOU, DR. PHILLIPS...
BUT I'M HAVING MY LUNCH
AT THIS TABLE,
HERE IN THE MIDDLE.
I'M HAVING MY LUNCH
RIGHT HERE
WITH MY GOOD FRIEND JOEY...
IF HE'LL SIT WITH ME.
I WILL SIT WITH YOU,
DR. GELLER.
YOU KNOW, WE WORK
IN A MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY
AND YET, THERE IS SOMETHING...
UNNATURAL
ABOUT THE WAY WE EAT LUNCH.
NOW...
I LOOK AROUND THIS CAFETERIA
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I SEE?
I SEE-I SEE DIVISION--
DIVISION BETWEEN PEOPLE
IN WHITE COATS
AND PEOPLE IN BLUE BLAZERS
AND I ASK MYSELF,
"MY GOD, WHY?!"
NOW, I SAY WE SHED
THESE-THESE COATS
THAT SEPARATE US
AND WE GET
TO KNOW THE PEOPLE UNDERNEATH.
I'M ROSS.
I'M DIVORCED
AND I HAVE A KID.
I'M JOEY.
I'M AN ACTOR.
I DON'T KNOW SQUAT
ABOUT DINOSAURS.
I'M TED AND I JUST
MOVED HERE A MONTH AGO
AND NEW YORK
REALLY SCARES ME.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE YOU GO!
YEAH. YOU HANG
IN THERE, TEDDY.
I'M ANDREW...
AND I DIDN'T PAY
FOR THIS PEAR.
OKAY. GOOD-GOOD FOR YOU.
I'M RHONDA...
AND THESE AREN'T REAL!
WOW, RHONDA.
UH...
I'M SCOTT...
YEAH. OKAY, SCOTT!
AND I NEED
TO FLIP THE LIGHT SWITCH
ON AND OFF 17 TIMES
BEFORE I LEAVE A ROOM
OR MY FAMILY WILL DIE.
MY MOM'S GOING TO
BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I CAN'T GIVE HIM UP.
( sighs )
YES. NO, I CAN.
I DON'T WANT TO...
BUT I CAN.
NO.
OH, I CAN'T WATCH THIS.
IT'S LIKE SOPHIE'S CHOICE.
YOU KNOW, I
NEVER SAW THAT.
OH, IT WAS ONLY OKAY.
( Phoebe groaning )
I CAN'T DO THIS.
MY MOM WAS RIGHT.
IF I CAN'T,
IF I CAN'T GIVE HIM UP
THEN... THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN GIVE UP A LITTLE BABY.
OH, GOD, FRANK AND ALICE
ARE GOING TO BE SO CRUSHED.
WH-WHAT ELSE,
WHAT ELSE CAN I GIVE THEM?
A KIDNEY.
HI.
All:
UM, WE WERE JUST IN
THE NEIGHBORHOOD, SO...
SO WE JUST THOUGHT
WE'D STOP BY
AND LET YOU KNOW
THERE'S STILL NO PRESSURE.
Alice:
NONE, BUT
IF THERE WAS
SOMETHING YOU
WANTED TO TELL US
WE'RE JUST GOING
TO BE RIGHT OVER
THERE HAVING COFFEE.
OKAY.
OH, WHO'S THIS LITTLE GUY?
OH. OH!
UM...
OH, HE'S SO CUTE.
HE REMINDS ME
OF MY OLD DOG, TUMOR.
OH, OH.
( Frank laughing )
YOU ARE SO PRECIOUS. I
COULD JUST TAKE YOU HOME.
( Frank laughing )
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
UH-HUH. YEAH.
OH...
OH, THANKS.
( laughing )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NO. I'M REALLY
OKAY WITH THIS.
YOU KNOW WHY?
'CAUSE LOOK AT THEM.
LOOK HOW HAPPY
THEY ARE...
AND I MADE THAT, SO, YOU KNOW...
I KNOW IT'S GOING TO BE, LIKE
A MILLION TIMES HARDER
TO GIVE UP A BABY
BUT, OH, MY GOD
IT'S GOING TO FEEL, LIKE,
A MILLION TIMES BETTER, RIGHT?
I'M WANT TO DO THIS.
I WANT TO CARRY YOUR BABY.
OH...
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
THIS MEANS TO US.
OH...
OH, MY GOD,
I THINK I'M GOING TO CRY.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S GOING
TO BE SO GREAT.
UH-HUH.
HI.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH! I-I GAVE THEM
THE PUPPY
AND IT MADE THEM SO HAPPY
THAT I DECIDED I'M GOING
TO CARRY THEIR BABY.
UH, PHOEBE...
NO, NO, I KNOW.
YOU AND I ARE TOTALLY
DIFFERENT PEOPLE, THOUGH
AND THIS IS
A TOTALLY DIFFERENT SITUATION
AND I KNOW THAT
I AM NOT GOING TO REGRET THIS.
OH, I-I UNDERSTAND ALL THAT.
IT'S JUST...
THAT WAS MY PUPPY.
OH...
WOULD YOU SURROGATE?
IT DEPENDS WHO ASKED.
WHAT IF I ASKED?
OH, MON...
SURE.
REALLY?
YES.
YOU'RE NOT ASKING ME, ARE YOU?
NO.
YES, TOTALLY.
( gasps )
THANK YOU.
YES! THANK YOU!
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]